https://www.tafn.org.uk/privacy-policy

At the accessible friends network, we are committed to protecting your privacy online. We protect any personal information you give us while you use our website.
We have included changes to address the new standards introduced by the European Data Protection Law known as the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).
Should you have any questions or concerns please contact our data controller Officer Michelle Collins. Enter Here TO Contact
Our Data Controller Officer By continuing to use this site you are signifying your agreement to the terms of this privacy policy.
What Personal information do we hold:
Your full Name,
Date OF Birth,
Email Address,
Postal Address,
Telephone Number,
Mobile telephone number,
TeamTalk user Name,
TeamTalk Password,
Website user name,
Your IP Address,
Bank details,
Skype name,
We collect personal information when you
register with us.
How do we use your information?
We use your personal details to provide you with the information, administrative purposes and
services TAFN has to offer.
The accessible friends network is responsible for collecting your personal information.
Any information we collect is stored safely online and is password
protected,
All personal information is
stored
for your term with us and is deleted safely
after 30 days of your leaving The Accessible Friends Network.
Who has access to your personal data:
The
trustees have the following access,
Your full Name,
Date OF Birth,
Email Address,
Postal Address,
Telephone Number,
Mobile telephone number,
Your IP Address,
The Treasurer and Vice Treasurer:
Also has access to your Bank details,
Membership officer and
Vice
memberships,
Your full Name,
Date OF Birth,
Email Address,
Postal Address,
Telephone Number,
Mobile phone number,
Your IP Address,
TeamTalk User name,
TeamTalk password,
Website username,
Skype name if given.
Help Desk Team:
Your full Name,
Email Address,
Telephone number,
Mobile telephone number,
Username for website and TeamTalk,
TeamTalk Password only,
Your IP Address,
Skype name if given.
No data is shared
with third parties or used in any other way (other than described in this policy or as required by law) unless you agree.
We reserve the right to share your personal information if we are legally obliged to,
and to enable us to apply our terms and conditions and other agreements.
Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet is 100 per cent secure. As a result, while we endeavour to protect your personal information, TAFN cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.
When we collect your personal information we use strict procedures and security features to prevent unauthorized access.
Privacy and comments
The posting of personal information  on our communicator,  website, email,  and  mailing lists
means your information is accessible to our members.
TAFN can not be responsible for  any postings or email messages
We strongly recommend you avoid sharing any personal information.
Accessing and updating your personal information held by  TAFN
You can ask us what information we hold about you by contacting our data controller officer Michelle Collins. Enter Here TO Contact
Our Data Controller Officer
Please keep your information up to date by editing your profile.
Enter Here TO Edit Your Profile
Changes to this policy:
We may change our privacy policy from time to time, But you will be notified of the changes straight away.
Enter Here To Return TO TAFN Home Page
